[Music] There
is a special category in ICICI Prove MF
and that category is Shareholders
Quota.  Now share holder quota means if you
have shares of ICICI Bank then
you become eligible for share holder quota
because it is a subsidiary company of ICICI Bank.
Ok?  And in this case, you have the
opportunity to install two applications under the same name.
Listen carefully.  If you apply for two applications in the same name,
you will apply for shareholder quota
and when will you be considered a shareholder? If the
record date was 5th December,
if you had
ICICI Bank shares in your demat account on 5th December, then you
can apply for shareholder quota.
Ok?  You can apply there.
How much first class can I do?  You can apply for a minimum of six shares worth Rs
12,990 and a
maximum of 90 shares worth Rs
1994850.
You have to make
one application within the shareholder quota of Rs 2 lakh and this will be accepted.
You have to put the second application in the retail category.  Have to
put it in HAI.
You can put it in whatever you want.  There
is no problem.  You
can put in retail plus share holder.
Can be invested in HAI Plus share holder.  This means that the share
holder category has become an extra one for you.
Well,
which can ensure your allotment.
Meaning, for this they have
kept approximately 5% quota which is the shareholder quota.
So 5% allotment
is reserved for shareholder quota.  He will definitely get that much.  If it is
filled too much then you will get proportionate
and if it is filled only that much then you will get as much as you
want.  So this is a way to install an additional application.
If you are a shareholder of ICICI Bank.  You
can apply in two categories.  A retail or HAI whatever you do.
Secondly, you can apply for
shareholder quota and submit an application up to ₹ lakh
there.  5%
reserve is kept for that.  But there
is no discount.
Many times, if someone comes and is a shareholder, then as soon as he
comes, his mouth starts watering.  If you get 5% or 10%
discount then the discount is
nothing.  ICICI Bank does not offer discounts.
This is also the IPO of ICICI Prove Mutual
Fund, its valuations have been
kept very attractive.  Otherwise, generally there is no
discount, till now
ICICI Bank has been seen bringing
IPO with a lot of stretch in their valuation.  But this time the pricing of the IPO has been done properly.  You will
also
get benefit from that.  But no discount for individual shareholders.